Leszek¹ Pietrzak

• Birthday: January 21st, 1987

• **Current location**: Warsaw, Poland (52°14′N 21°1′E)

• Nationality: Polish

Phone: <u>skype:smutnyleszek</u>

• **E-mail**: smutnyleszek@gmail.com

• Website: github.com/smutnyleszek

• Favourite color: black

¹if in doubt, try "lesheck"

I am a creator, I always loved building something new: be it through writing, drawing or coding. As for frontend development, I love that my work can be experienced live in the browser and that I can publish anything in just a few minutes.

The three values closest to my heart are: order, meaning and simplicity. I fear for the future of humanity, so I don't want to throw more senseless evil out there - I would love to take part in a meaningful, nature- and future-friendly projects. I try to maintain good work/life balance, so I avoid toxic environments.

Skills

I have strong frontend development skills with some backend experience. I can do identity design, UI design and illustration - I mainly use Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign. I am no stranger to Scrum, Kanban, recruitment, introducing new people into projects and copywriting. I'm familiar with all the OSs, but my favourite setup is MacOS with Atom.

Technologies I would love to work with: **ES6**, **Angular**, **React**, **NPM**, **cssnext** and **Jekyll**. I would also like to have **TDD**, **code reviews**, **pair programming** and good planning with estimations.

Some technologies I worked with: HTML (Twig), CSS (Compass, Sass, cssnext, BEM, MADCSS), JavaScript (CoffeeScript, ES6 [Babel], Angular, React, Alt, Backbone, Phaser, Lodash, jQuery, TweenMax), TDD (Karma, Jasmine, PhantomJS), Grunt, NPM, Git, CEF, Jekyll, MySQL, PHP (Symfony2), Jira, Asana.

Employment

November 2014 - Present

Frontend Engineer @ GOG.com - Warsaw, Poland - gog.com/galaxy

My main responsibility was creating a frontend of GOG Galaxy desktop application. I also develop some webapps and take part in recruiting new developers and introducing them to the project. During work here I took part in launching GOG Galaxy and creating The Witcher 3 game.

Technologies: ES6, Angular, Lodash, TDD (Karma, Jasmine, PhantomJS), Twig, Sass, BEM, MADCSS, CoffeeScript, Grunt, NPM, Git, CEF, Jira, Asana

March 2007 - Present

Illustrator, Designer & Web Developer @ Self-employment - Worldwide - <u>leszekpietrzak.com</u>

I'm always open for small design and web jobs to give me opportunity to do something crazy and try something new. I also work on some open-source projects and tools on my spare time. Some cool web projects are:

- Hues color converter tool (React, Alt, ES6, RequireJS, Karma, cssnext, MADCSS)
- Akabusk simple OMDb movie finder (Angular, ES6, Karma, cssnext, MADCSS)
- Mad Skeleton CSS boilerplate (Jekyll, Node, cssnext, MADCSS)
- <u>HashTabber</u> hashchange-driven tabbed content switcher (ES5, Compass)

June 2013 - November 2014

Web Designer & Frontend Developer @ Clos Brothers - Warsaw, Poland - closbrothers.pl

I was working in a small team delivering websites and webapps for big clients (Toyota) and smaller, educational ones, too (Museum of the History of Polish Jews, Silesian Risings Museum).

Technologies: Angular, Phaser, jQuery, TweenMax, Compass, Jekyll, Twig, Symfony2, PHP, Grunt, Git, SVN.

October 2012 - July 2013

Graphic Designer & Web Developer @ Trewebs - Warsaw, Poland - trewebs.com

In this semi-startup, I was hired to design the UI and identity for diet app. As time went on, there were less design tasks and a need for developer arisen - as I was already familiar with HTML and CSS, I started to learn and work on some small web development projects.

Technologies: jQuery, Compass, Drupal, WordPress, PHP, MySQL

Education

September 2010 - September 2013

Graphic Design @ Wyższa Szkoła Nauk Humanistycznych i Dziennikarstwa - Poznań, Poland

Licentiate degree (~BA) with highest score (5)

September 2007 - September 2010

Cultural Studies @ Wyższa Szkoła Nauk Humanistycznych i Dziennikarstwa - Poznań, Poland

September 2006 - September 2007

Computer Science @ Adam Mickiewicz University - Poznań, Poland

Language skills

- Polish native
- English professional
- **German** basics
- Toki Pona basics

Interests

Evolution of life, existential philosophy, traditional tattoo, ambient music, fantastic literature, American B-movies, Haiku, contemporary art and European comics.